Inventory of the William J. Casey papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- WRITINGS ADDENDUM, 1942-1989 (Boxes 428-459)
  - Bibliography (Box-folder 428: 1)
  - "Business at War," Washington Post, 1942 March 28 (Box-folder 428: 2)
  - "Mail Prospecting for More Sales," typescript, circa 1955 (Box-folder 428: 3)
  - Estate Plans, forms and correspondence, 1959? (Box-folder 428: 4)
  - "Insurance in Commercial Transactions," typescript, 1960s (Box-folder 428: 5)
  - "Unsecured Creditors," typescript, 1960s (Box-folder 428: 6)
  - Untitled writing on charities and foundations, typescript and notes, 1960s (Box-folder 428: 7)
  - Untitled writing on history of Christianity, typescript and notes, 1961? (Box-folder 428: 8)
  - Real Estate Exchanges and How to Make Them, 1963 (Box-folder 428: 9)
    Correspondence
  - "Cathedrals, Monasteries, and Castles," typescript and notes, 1965 (Box-folder 428: 10)
  - Lawyer's Desk Book, drafts and correspondence, 1965? (Box-folder 428: 11)
  - The Truth about Probate and Family Financial Planning: How to Build and Preserve Your Wealth, 1967 (Box-folder 428: 12)
  - Successful Compensation Techniques that Build Executive Fortunes, 1968 (Box-folder 428: 13)
  - "Huge Responsibilities Await the Investment Business in the Coming Decade: Many Changes in Store," [National Securities Traders Association publication], 1971 (Box-folder 428: 14)
  - "Corporate Responsibility as Seen from the SEC," Business and Society Review, 1972 Spring (Box-folder 428: 15)
  - "The SEC, from the Top," Newsday, 1972 December 24 (Box-folder 428: 16)
  - The Clandestine War in Europe, 1942-1945 (pamphlet), 1974 (Box-folder 429: 1)
  - Proposed memoir of William J. Donovan, 1975 (Box-folder 429: 2)
    Correspondence and working materials
  - "Investment and Trade in the Pacific Basin," in Proceedings of the Republic of China-U.S. Conference on Investment Trade and Tourism, 1976 (Box-folder 429: 3)
  - Where and How the War Was Fought: An Armchair Tour of the American Revolution, 1976
    - Contract and publisher correspondence (Box-folder 429: 4)
    - Typescript (Box-folder 429: 5-6)
    - Typescript (contd.) (Box-folder 430: 1-2)
    - Galleys (Box-folder 430: 3)
    - Congratulatory letters (Box-folder 430: 4)
  - "A New Look at Municipal Bonds: Disclosure Responsibilities in the Municipal Bond Market" (with Owen T. Smith), St. John's Law Review, 1976 Summer (Box-folder 430: 5)
    Printed copies and correspondence
  - "Energy and National Security," in Frank N. Trager, ed., Oil, Divestiture and National Security, 1977 (Box-folder 430: 6)
  - "SEC Rules 144 and 146 Revisited," Brooklyn Law Review, 1977 Spring (Box-folder 430: 7)
  - "Common Sense and the CIA," typescript, circa 1978 (Box-folder 430: 8)
  - "Leonard W. Hall, RIP," National Review, 1979 June 22 (Box-folder 430: 9)
  - "How to Read a Book," typescript, 1982 September 18 (Box-folder 430: 10)
  - What We Face, (pamphlet), 1983 (Box-folder 430: 11)
  - "The Health of U.S. Intelligence," Signal, 1984 May (Box-folder 430: 12)
  - "The Other Side of the Coin," Leaders, 1984 July-August-September (Box-folder 430: 13)
  - Untitled book-length writing on military strategy and intelligence in the American Revolution, 1986
    - Drafts
      - 1982 (Box-folder 431: 1)
      - 1983 (Box-folder 431: 2)
      - 1984 (Richard Gambino collaboration) (Box-folder 431: 3-4)
      - 1986 (Box-folder 431: 5-6)
      - 1986 (contd.) (Box-folder 432: 1-3)
      - 1986 (David Franke collaboration) (Box-folder 432: 4)
  - Background material
    - Printed matter (Box-folder 432: 5-6)
    - Ashcraft, Allan C., "General George Washington and the Evolution of a Military Intelligence Service during the American Revolution" (Box-folder 433: 1)
  - "Scouting the Future," Presidential Studies Quarterly, 1986 Summer (Box-folder 433: 2)
  - "Intelligence and the Media," typescript and correspondence, 1986 August 21 (Box-folder 433: 3)
  - "The Peak of Creativity," RMCPA [Rocky Mountain College Placement Association] Diggin's, printed copy, 1986 Fall (Box-folder 433: 4)
  - "Supercomputers on the Way to the CIA," Computerworld, printed copy, 1986 November 3 (Box-folder 433: 5)
  - "The Heritage and Relevance of Teddy Roosevelt," in The Nassau County Council of the Boy Scouts of America, 1917-1987: A Pictorial History (Box-folder 433: 6)
  - The Secret War against Hitler, 1988
    - Drafts (Box-folder 433: 7-9)
    - Drafts (contd.) (Box 434-439)
    - Drafts (contd.) (Box-folder 440: 1-2)
    - Notes (Box-folder 440: 3-5)
    - Notes (contd.) (Box-folder 441: 1-3)
    - Research correspondence
      - 1965-1975 (Box-folder 441: 4)
      - 1976 (Box-folder 442: 1)
      - 1977 (Box-folder 442: 2-3)
      - 1978 (Box-folder 443: 1-2)
      - 1979 (Box-folder 443: 3)
      - 1980-1987 (Box-folder 443: 4)
    - Foreword by O. C. Doering, Jr. (Box-folder 443: 5)
    - Expenses (Box-folder 443: 6)
    - Publisher correspondence (Box-folder 443: 7)
    - Reviews (Box-folder 443: 8)
    - Posthumous correspondence (Box-folder 443: 9)
    - Background material used in preparation of the book
      - Photocopies of Office of Strategic Services and other military documents, obtained mainly from the National Archives (Box 444-452)
      - Unpublished studies, memoirs, speeches, transcriptions, translations, and fragments (Box 453-455)
      - Printed matter (contd.) (Box 456-457)
      - Printed matter (contd.) (Box-folder 458: 1-3)
    - Scouting the Future: The Public Speeches of William J. Casey, 1989
      - Drafts (Box-folder 458: 4)
      - Drafts (contd.) (Box-folder 459: 1)
      - Preface by Leo Cherne (Box-folder 459: 2)
      - Publisher and posthumous correspondence, and publication notice (Box-folder 459: 3)
- EARLY LIFE FILE, 1913-1943 (Box 459)
  - Saint Agnes Academic School (Rockville Centre, New York) annual, 1928 (Box-folder 459: 4)
  - Fordham University yearbook, 1934 (Box-folder 459: 5)
  - Ward-Stilson Company correspondence and financial documents, 1943 (Box-folder 459: 6)
  - Miscellany. Clipping and personal documents (Box-folder 459: 7)
- OFFICE OF STRATEGIC SERVICES FILE ADDENDUM, 1943-1945 (Box 460)
  - Applications and letters of recommendation (Box-folder 460: 1)
  - Personnel records (Box-folder 460: 2)
  - Operational reports and correspondence (Box-folder 460: 3)
  - Discharge and citations. Includes letter of commendation by William J. Donovan (Box-folder 460: 4)
- PRE-GOVERNMENT CAREER FILE ADDENDUM, 1945-1971 (Boxes 460-480)
  - Speeches and engagements
    Correspondence, itineraries, programs, and meeting materials. Speech transcripts are noted when present
    - European trip, 1958 August 1-September 10 (Box-folder 460: 5)
    - Fordham University alumni meeting, circa 1959 (Box-folder 460: 6)
    - Fordham University class of 1934 silver jubilee banquet, New York City, 1959 June 6 (Box-folder 460: 7)
    - European trip, 1961 June 30-September 15 (Box-folder 460: 8)
    - Catholic Charities Bishop's Dinner, Garden City, New York, 1965 May 8 (Box-folder 460: 9)
    - Long Island Association Executives breakfast, Plainview, New York, 1966 January 5 (Box-folder 460: 10)
    - Fordham College Alumni Association Achievement Awards dinner, New York City, 1966 May 22 (Box-folder 460: 11)
    - Addison C. Harris Lecture, Indiana University School of Law, Bloomington, 1967 November 3 (Box-folder 460: 12)
    - Jesuit colleges boards meeting on changing legal status, Le Moyne College, Syracuse, New York, 1968 April 27-28 (Box-folder 460: 13)
    - Long Island Association of Commerce and Industry annual meeting, Bethpage, New York, 1969 October 1 (Box-folder 460: 14)
    - Unidentified speeches (Box-folder 460: 15)
  - Correspondence
    - Aubrey, James T., Jr. (Box-folder 461: 1)
    - Dade, George (Box-folder 461: 2)
    - Donovan, William J. (Box-folder 461: 3)
    - Guylay, L. Richard (Box-folder 461: 4)
    - Lichenstein, C. M. (Box-folder 461: 5)
    - Michalos, Constantine A. (Box-folder 461: 6)
    - Mooney, Michael M. (Box-folder 461: 7)
    - Naster, Bert (Box-folder 461: 8)
    - Nixon, Richard M., and Nixon presidential administration officials (Box-folder 461: 9)
    - Thorne, Landon K. (Box-folder 461: 10)
    - U (Box-folder 461: 11)
    - V (Box-folder 461: 12)
    - W (Box-folder 461: 13)
    - Webster, Giles Anthony (Box-folder 461: 14)
    - Weiss, Charles H. (Box-folder 461: 15)
    - Wiersma, John W. (Box-folder 461: 16)
    - Winkler, Martin (Box-folder 461: 17)
    - Wormser, René A. (Box-folder 461: 18)
    - Yassen, Leonard C. (Box-folder 461: 19)
    - Zagarino, William C. (Box-folder 461: 20)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 461: 21)
  - Certificates (Box-folder 461: 22)
  - Financial records, miscellaneous (Box-folder 461: 23)
  - Lists and addresses (Box-folder 462: 1)
  - Powers of attorney (Box-folder 462: 2)
  - Publicity clippings (Box-folder 462: 3)
  - Telephone logs
    - 1968 (Box-folder 462: 4)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 462: 5)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 462: 6)
  - Subject file. Correspondence, memoranda, reports, legal and financial records, and printed matter
    - Advancement Devices Company (Box-folder 462: 7)
    - Aero-Chatillon Corporation (Box-folder 462: 8)
    - Agro Resources, Inc. (Box-folder 462: 9)
    - Atlas Acceptance Corporation (Box-folder 463: 1)
    - Bar associations (Box-folder 463: 2)
    - Benson Laboratories (Box-folder 463: 3)
    - Blyth and Company (Box-folder 463: 4)
    - Bonds (Box-folder 463: 5)
    - Books and publishing (Box-folder 463: 6)
    - Buildings and leases (Box-folder 463: 7)
    - Business Reports, Inc. (Box-folder 463: 8)
    - C. Bertelsmann Verlag (Box-folder 463: 9)
    - Cable television (Box-folder 463: 10)
    - Camco, Inc. (Box-folder 463: 11)
    - Can-Amera Oil Sands Company (Box-folder 463: 12)
    - Capital Cities Television Corporation (Box-folder 463: 13)
    - Capitol Towers (apartment complex, Sacramento, California) (Box-folder 464: 1-4)
    - Casey Hereford Farms (Box-folder 465: 1-6)
    - Charities and tax-exempt foundations (Box-folder 466: 1-4)
    - COAP Systems (Box-folder 466: 5)
    - Cobra Petroleum Company (Box-folder 467: 1)
    - Communication Channels, Inc. (Box-folder 467: 2)
    - Communitron, Inc. (Box-folder 467: 3)
    - Community Communications of Nassau County (Box-folder 467: 4)
    - ComputerPix Corporation (Box-folder 467: 5)
    - Computers (Box-folder 467: 6)
    - Continental Air Services--Micronesian operations (Box-folder 467: 7)
    - Copy Research Corporation (Box-folder 467: 8)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (Box-folder 467: 9)
    - Cybetronics, Inc. (Box-folder 467: 10)
    - David L. Babson and Company (Box-folder 468: 1)
    - Detwiler Development Corporation (Box-folder 468: 2)
    - Diebold, Inc. (Box-folder 468: 3)
    - Digest of Tax Articles (Box-folder 468: 4)
    - Economic Cooperation Administration (Box-folder 468: 5)
    - Educational Development and Research Corporation (Box-folder 468: 6)
    - Elections
      - 1952 (Dwight D. Eisenhower presidential campaign). (Box-folder 468: 7)
        Includes post-election analysis
      - 1958 (Leonard W. Hall New York gubernatorial campaign) (Box-folder 468: 8)
      - 1960 (Richard M. Nixon presidential campaign) (Box-folder 469: 1)
      - 1964 (potential Richard M. Nixon presidential campaign) (Box-folder 469: 2)
      - 1968 (Richard M. Nixon presidential campaign). (Box-folder 469: 3)
        Task Force on Tax Policy report
    - Encounter (Box-folder 469: 4)
    - Engelhard Minerals and Chemicals Corporation (Box-folder 469: 5)
    - Exchange Fund of Boston (Box-folder 469: 6)
    - Fidelity Bank of Colonie (Box-folder 469: 7)
    - Fields (Harry R.) lawsuit (Box-folder 469: 8)
    - Film 'n File, Inc. (Box-folder 469: 9)
    - First Investment Annuity Company of America (Box-folder 470: 1-4)
    - First National Bank of Highland (Box-folder 471: 1)
    - Fluid Metering, Inc. (Box-folder 471: 2)
    - Fordham University (Box-folder 471: 3)
    - Founders Mutual Deposit Corporation (Box-folder 471: 4)
    - Franklin National Bank (Box-folder 471: 5)
    - Glore Forgan, Wm. R. Staats, Inc. (Box-folder 471: 6-9)
    - Good Counsel College (Box-folder 471: 10)
    - Hall, Casey, Dickler and Howley (law firm) (Box-folder 472: 1-2)
    - Hament Associates (Box-folder 472: 3)
    - Hickey, Walter (Box-folder 472: 4)
    - Hico Corporation of America (Box-folder 472: 5)
    - Hiram Walker and Sons, Inc. (Box-folder 472: 6)
    - Holle Verlag (Box-folder 472: 7)
    - Hunting Towers Associates (Box-folder 472: 8)
    - Hunting Towers Associates (contd.) (Box-folder 473: 1)
    - Industrial Electronics Associates (Box-folder 473: 2)
    - Institute for Business Planning (Box-folder 473: 3-5)
    - Institute for Business Planning (contd.) (Box-folder 474: 1)
    - Inter vivos trusts (Box-folder 474: 2)
    - International Life Insurance Company of Buffalo (Box-folder 474: 3)
    - Investment Annuity, Inc. (Box-folder 474: 4)
    - Investment Appraisal Company (Box-folder 474: 5)
    - Investment Trust of Boston (Box-folder 474: 6)
    - Investments, Miscellaneous (Box-folder 474: 7)
    - Investors Capital Exchange Fund (Box-folder 474: 8)
    - Investors Planning Corporation of America (Box-folder 474: 9-10)
    - Investors Planning Corporation of America (contd.) (Box-folder 475: 1)
    - Ivanhoe Associates (Box-folder 475: 2)
    - J. K. Lasser Company (Box-folder 475: 3)
    - Kal/Equipment Corporation (Box-folder 475: 4)
    - Kalvar Corporation (Box-folder 475: 5)
    - Key Color Studios (Box-folder 475: 6)
    - Kinetics Corporation (Box-folder 475: 7)
    - Kingsbridge Shopping Plaza Company (Box-folder 475: 8)
    - Kingsbury, Alan P. (Box-folder 475: 9)
    - Ku Klux Klan (Box-folder 476: 1)
    - Kybe Corporation (Box-folder 476: 2)
    - La Belle Industries (Box-folder 476: 3)
    - Laird and Company (Box-folder 476: 4)
    - Langan Aperture Cards, Inc. (Box-folder 476: 5)
    - Laser Link Corporation (Box-folder 476: 6)
    - Life insurance (Box-folder 476: 7)
    - Long Island Commercial Review (Box-folder 476: 8)
    - Long Island Lighting Company (Box-folder 476: 9)
    - McCurdy-Trammell oil properties (Box-folder 476: 10)
    - McCurdy-Trammell oil properties (contd.) (Box-folder 477: 1)
    - McDaniel and Shapiro estate tax cases (Box-folder 477: 2)
    - Meridian Capital Corporation (Box-folder 477: 3)
    - Mill Creek Oil Company (Box-folder 477: 4)
    - Monthly Digest of Legal Articles (Box-folder 477: 5)
    - National Club Association (Box-folder 477: 6)
    - National Design Center (Box-folder 477: 7)
    - National Patent Development Corporation (Box-folder 478: 1)
    - National Strategy Information Center (Box-folder 478: 2)
    - Ogden Corporation (Box-folder 478: 3)
    - Olsten Corporation (Box-folder 478: 4)
    - Paine, John (Box-folder 478: 5)
    - Patents (Box-folder 478: 6)
    - Patrician Paper Company (Box-folder 478: 7)
    - Photomedia Company (Box-folder 478: 8)
    - Plan America Fund (Box-folder 478: 9)
    - Practising Law Institute (Box-folder 478: 10)
    - Prentice-Hall, Inc. (Box-folder 478: 11)
    - R. S. Ellsworth, Inc. (Hawaiian property) (Box-folder 478: 12)
    - Radio Corporation of America (Box-folder 478: 13)
    - Raychem Corporation (Box-folder 478: 14)
    - Republican Party (Box-folder 478: 15)
    - Research and Documentation Corporation (Box-folder 479: 1)
    - Ridgely Realty Company (Box-folder 479: 2)
    - Roosevelt Raceway (Box-folder 479: 3)
    - Sealed Air Corporation (Box-folder 479: 4)
    - Second Centennial Fund (Box-folder 479: 5)
    - Securities and Exchange Commission (Box-folder 479: 6)
    - Sinclair-Koppers Company (Box-folder 479: 7)
    - South African investments (Box-folder 479: 8)
    - Stocks (Box-folder 479: 9)
    - Thomas J. Moran's Sons, Inc. (Box-folder 480: 1)
    - Thomas O'Connell Management and Research Corporation (Box-folder 480: 2)
    - Transamerica Corporation (Box-folder 480: 3)
    - United Fund of Long Island (Box-folder 480: 4)
    - United Jewish Appeal (Box-folder 480: 5)
    - United States Naval Reserve (Box-folder 480: 6)
    - United States Trust Company (Box-folder 480: 7)
    - Universal Reference System (Box-folder 480: 8)
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. (Box-folder 480: 9)
    - WROW (Television station) (Box-folder 480: 10)
    - Waldemar Medical Research Foundation (Box-folder 480: 11)
    - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (Box-folder 480: 12)
    - Westminster Fund (Box-folder 480: 13)
    - Who's Who in America (Box-folder 480: 14)
  - Miscellany (Box-folder 480: 15)
- CASEY FOR CONGRESS COMMITTEE FILE ADDENDUM, 1966 (Box 481)
  - Campaign leaflets (Box-folder 481: 1)
  - Position papers (Box-folder 481: 2)
  - Correspondence (Box-folder 481: 3)
  - Memoranda (Box-folder 481: 4)
  - Financial records (Box-folder 481: 5)
  - Voter opinion poll responses (Box-folder 481: 6)
  - Press coverage (Box-folder 481: 7)
- CASEY FOUNDATION FILE ADDENDUM, 1967-1977 (Boxes 481-485)
  - Certificate of amendment and resolutions (Box-folder 481: 8)
  - Council on Foundations correspondence (Box-folder 481: 9)
  - Publicity and press coverage (Box-folder 481: 10)
  - Applications and lists of awards
    - 1967 (Box-folder 481: 11)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 481: 12)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 481: 13)
    - 1969 (contd.) (Box-folder 482: 1)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 482: 2)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 482: 3-4)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 483: 1)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 483: 2)
  - Financial records
    - 1967 (Box-folder 483: 3-5)
    - 1968 (Box-folder 483: 6)
    - 1969 (Box-folder 483: 7-8)
    - 1969 (contd.) (Box-folder 484: 1)
    - 1970 (Box-folder 484: 2)
    - 1971 (Box-folder 484: 3)
    - 1972 (Box-folder 484: 4)
    - 1973 (Box-folder 484: 5)
    - 1975 (Box-folder 484: 6)
    - 1976 (Box-folder 484: 7)
  - Cancelled checks (Box-folder 484: 8, Folder 485: 1)
- SECURITIES AND EXCHANGE COMMISSION FILE ADDENDUM, 1971-1973 (Boxes 485-494)
  - Confirmation hearings. Letters of recommendation, and transcript of testimony before, and report of, the Senate Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs (Box-folder 485: 2)
  - Congratulatory letters upon appointment (Box-folder 485: 3)
  - Speeches and engagements. Correspondence, programs, and itineraries. Speeches are noted when present
    - Veterans of the O.S.S. dinner in honor of David Bruce, Washington D.C., 1971 May 26 (Box-folder 485: 4)
    - St. John's University convocation with honorary degree award to WJC, New York City, 1971 October 26 (Box-folder 485: 5)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews dinner in honor of WJC and others, New York City, 1971 November 1 (Box-folder 485: 6)
    - National Industrial Conference Board meeting, New York City, 1971 November 18 (Box-folder 485: 7)
    - Proposed trip to India, 1971 December (Box-folder 485: 8)
      Trip cancelled
    - Practising Law Institute session, Washington, D.C., 1972 February 18 (Box-folder 485: 9)
    - Georgetown Club party, Washington, D.C., 1972 March 24 (Box-folder 485: 10)
    - Conference on Financial Reporting, Paris, France, 1972 May 19 (Box-folder 485: 11)
    - Financial Analysts Federation meeting, New York City, 1972 May 22 (Box-folder 485: 12)
    - Trip to Ireland, 1972 May 26-June 7 (Box-folder 485: 13)
    - Commonwealth Club of California meeting, San Francisco, 1972 July 21 (Box-folder 485: 14)
    - Tax Institute session, Long Island University, Greenvale, New York, 1972 September 16 (Box-folder 485: 15)
    - Long Island Hall of Fame presentation to Leonard W. Hall, 1972 September 16 (Box-folder 485: 16)
    - Colorado Bar Association annual meeting, Colorado Springs, 1972 October 13 (Box-folder 485: 17)
    - Financial Executives Institute session, Las Vegas, Nevada, 1972 October 18 (Box-folder 485: 18)
    - Federal Tax Forum dinner in honor of WJC, New York City, 1972 November 21 (Box-folder 485: 19)
    - Inauguration of Richard M. Nixon for second term as President, Washington, D.C., 1973 January 20 (Box-folder 485: 20)
  - Personnel file. Includes Civil Service Commission correspondence (Box-folder 486: 1)
  - Addresses (Box-folder 486: 2)
  - Internal Securities and Exchange Commission memoranda (Box-folder 486: 3)
  - Reports of Securities and Exhange Commission Advisory Committees, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 486: 4)
    Bound volume
  - Report of Securities and Exchange Commission Real Estate Advisory Committee, 1972 October 12 (Box-folder 486: 5)
  - Institutional Investor Study Report of the Securities and Exchange Commission, 1971 March (Box-folder 487: 1)
    Page proofs
  - House Committee on Interstate and Foreign Commerce Subcommittee on Commerce and Finance. Study of the Securities Industry, 1971-1972. 6 volumes. Includes statements submitted by WJC
    - Parts 1-3 (Box-folder 487: 2)
    - Parts 4-6 (Box-folder 488: 1)
  - Correspondence
    - Cherne, Leo (Box-folder 488: 2)
    - Deak, Nicholas L. (Box-folder 488: 3)
    - E (Box-folder 488: 4)
    - Hoxie, R. Gordon (Box-folder 488: 5)
    - Kripke, Homer (Box-folder 488: 6)
    - Nixon, Richard M., and White House officials (Box-folder 488: 7)
    - O (Box-folder 488: 8)
    - Rose, Halleck L. (Box-folder 488: 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 488: 10)
  - Publicity. Press coverage of WJC
    - Biographical data (Box-folder 489: 1)
    - General (Box-folder 489: 2-5)
    - Business Week (Box-folder 490: 1)
    - Current Biography (Box-folder 490: 2)
    - Finance (Box-folder 490: 3)
    - Institutional Investor (Box-folder 490: 4)
    - Investor's Reader (Box-folder 490: 5)
      Includes transcript of interview of WJC in 1972 June 1 issue
    - Long Island Commercial Review (Box-folder 490: 6)
    - Trusts and Estates (Box-folder 490: 7)
    - Wall Street Letter (Box-folder 490: 8)
  - House Interstate and Foreign Commerce Committee Special Subcommittee on Investigations investigation into Commission actions with regard to International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation, 1972 September-December (Box-folder 490: 9)
    Includes transcript of testimony, and correspondence
  - Central Intelligence Agency. Basic Intelligence Factbook, 1972 (Box-folder 490: 10)
  - Subject file. Correspondence, memoranda, legal and financial records, and printed matter
    - Arms control (Box-folder 491: 1)
    - Bar Association of Nassau County (Box-folder 491: 2)
    - Blind trust (Box-folder 491: 3)
    - C and D Associates (Box-folder 491: 4)
    - COAP Systems (Box-folder 491: 5)
    - Capital Cities Broadcasting Corporation (Box-folder 491: 6)
    - Capital Management Associates (Box-folder 491: 7)
    - Capitol Towers (apartment complex, Sacramento, California) (Box-folder 491: 8)
    - Caps Equipment, Inc. (Box-folder 491: 9)
    - Community Communications of Nassau County (Box-folder 491: 10)
    - Conflicts of interest (Box-folder 491: 11)
    - Doundoulakis (Helias) lawsuit (Box-folder 491: 12)
    - Dowling College (Box-folder 491: 13)
    - Elections--1972 (Richard M. Nixon presidential campaign) (Box-folder 491: 14)
    - Electromechanical Devices, Inc. (Box-folder 491: 15)
    - Exchange Magazine (Box-folder 491: 16)
    - Federal City Club (Washington, D.C.) (Box-folder 491: 17)
    - Filmcard Corporation (Box-folder 491: 18)
    - Fluid Metering, Inc. (Box-folder 491: 19)
    - Gift taxation (Box-folder 491: 20)
    - Insurance Federation of New York State (Box-folder 491: 21)
    - Kennedy Center of the Performing Arts (Box-folder 491: 22)
    - Langan Aperture Cards, Inc. (Box-folder 492: 1-3)
    - Luxembourg (Box-folder 492: 4)
    - McCurdy Oil Company (Box-folder 492: 5)
    - McGovern (Eugene Vincent) estate (Box-folder 492: 6)
    - Multiponics Corporation (Box-folder 493: 1-3)
    - Prentice-Hall, Inc. (Box-folder 493: 4)
    - R. S. Ellsworth, Inc. (Box-folder 493: 5)
    - Research and Documentation Corporation (Box-folder 493: 6)